{"quiz":[

    {
        "question":
        "What programming language is primarily used for building Flutter apps?",
        "options": ["Java", "Python", "Dart", "JavaScript"],
        "answer":"Dart"
      },
      {
        "question":
        "Which widget is used for creating a scrollable list of items in Flutter?",
        "options": ["TextWidget", "ListView", "GridWidget", "Container"],
        "answer": "TextWidget"
      },
      {
        "question":
        "What is the purpose of the 'pubspec.yaml' file in a Flutter project?",
        "options": [
          "It defines the project's app icon.",
          "It specifies the project's dependencies.",
          "It controls the project's layout and design.",
          "It manages user authentication."
        ],
        "answer":"It specifies the project's dependencies."

      },
      {
        "question":
        "Which Flutter command is used to run the app on an Android emulator or device?",
        "options": [
          "flutter install",
          "flutter build",
          "flutter run",
          "flutter debug"
        ],
        "answer":"flutter run"

      },
      {
        "question":
        "What is the primary function of the MaterialApp widget in a Flutter app?",
        "options": [
          "Define the app's theme and layout.",
          "Create a new instance of the app.",
          "Handle user authentication.",
          "Manage state in the app."
        ],
        "answer":"Define the app's theme and layout."

      },
      {
        "question":
        "Which widget is used to display a modal bottom sheet in Flutter?",
        "options": [
          "AlertDialog",
          "BottomNavigationBar",
          "BottomSheet",
          "Scaffold"
        ],
        "answer":"BottomSheet"

      },
      {
        "question": "In Flutter, what does the term 'widget' refer to?",
        "options": [
          "A user's profile picture",
          "A small graphical component that can be combined to build the UI",
          "A unit of data storage",
          "A built-in Flutter app template"
        ],
        "answer":"A small graphical component that can be combined to build the UI"

      },
      {
        "question":
        "Which package is commonly used for handling HTTP requests in Flutter?",
        "options": ["http_requests", "network_io", "http_client", "http"],
        "answer": "http"
      },
      {
        "question":
        "What is the primary purpose of the StatefulWidget class in Flutter?",
        "options": [
          "To create a stateless widget",
          "To store mutable state data that can change over time",
          "To define the app's theme",
          "To handle user authentication"
        ],
        "answer":"To store mutable state data that can change over time"

      },
      {
        "question":
        "Which widget is used for creating a tabbed navigation interface in Flutter?",
        "options": ["TabView", "TabBar", "TabLayout", "TabNavigator"],
        "answer":"TabBar"
      }
]}